<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Prosty notatnik</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Notatnik</string>
    <string name="widget_config">Dziękujemy za korzystanie z aplikacji.\nPo więcej prostych aplikacji, takich jak ta, udaj się na SimpleMobileTools.com.</string>
    <string name="cannot_share_empty_text">Nie mogę udostępnić pustej notatki</string>
    <string name="simple_note">Prosta notatka</string>
    <string name="new_note">Dodaj nową notatkę</string>
    <string name="no_title">Nazwij swoją notatkę</string>
    <string name="title_taken">Notatka o tej nazwie już istnieje</string>
    <string name="open_note">Otwórz notatkę</string>
    <string name="delete_note">Usuń notatkę</string>
    <string name="delete_note_prompt_message">Czy na pewno chcesz usunąć notatkę \"%s\"?</string>
    <string name="pick_a_note">Wybierz notatkę</string>
    <string name="rename_note">Zmień nazwę notatki</string>
    <string name="general_note">Notatka ogólna</string>
    <string name="create_new_note">Utwórz nową notatkę</string>
    <string name="add_to_note">Dodaj do notatki</string>
    <string name="unsaved_changes_warning">You have some unsaved changes. What do you want to do with them?</string>
    <string name="note_shown_widget">Note shown in the widget:</string>
    <string name="new_note_type">New note type:</string>
    <string name="text_note">Text note</string>

    <!-- File notes -->
    <string name="open_file">Otwórz plik</string>
    <string name="export_as_file">Wyeksportuj jako plik</string>
    <string name="file_too_large">Plik jest za duży (może mieć co najwyżej 1 MB)</string>
    <string name="only_import_file_content">Zaimportuj tylko zawartość pliku\n(zmiana pliku nie będzie miała wpływu na notatkę)</string>
    <string name="update_file_at_note">Zaktualizuj plik po zaktualizowaniu notatki\n(notatka zostanie usunięta jeśli plik zostanie usunięty lub zmieni się jego lokalizacja)</string>
    <string name="delete_file_itself">Usuń także plik \"%s\"</string>
    <string name="note_saved_successfully">Notatka \"%s\" została zapisana</string>
    <string name="note_exported_successfully">Notatka \"%s\" została eksportowana</string>
    <string name="only_export_file_content">Only export the current file content\n(changing the note will not affect the file)</string>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="display_success_message">Wyświetlaj informacje o pomyślnym zapisaniu notatki</string>
    <string name="links_and_emails_clickable">Przetwarzaj linki i adresy e-mail do klikalnej formy.</string>
    <string name="place_cursor_end">Umieszczaj kursor na końcu notatki</string>
    <string name="monospaced_font">Używaj czcionki o stałej szerokości</string>
    <string name="show_keyboard">Pokazuj klawiaturę na starcie</string>
    <string name="show_word_count">Pokazuj liczbę słów</string>
    <string name="show_character_count">Show character count</string>
    <string name="alignment">Wyrównanie tekstu w notatkach</string>
    <string name="left">Do lewej strony</string>
    <string name="center">Do środka</string>
    <string name="right">Do prawej strony</string>
    <string name="widget_note">Notatka używana w widżecie</string>
    <string name="show_note_picker">Pokazuj wybór notatki po uruchomieniu</string>
    <string name="autosave_notes">Autozapis notatek</string>
    <string name="enable_line_wrap">Zawijanie linii</string>
    <string name="use_incognito_mode">Use Incognito mode of keyboards</string>
    <string name="move_undone_checklist_items">Move undone checklist items at the top</string>

    <!-- Checklists -->
    <string name="checklist">Checklist</string>
    <string name="add_new_checklist_item">Add a new checklist item</string>
    <string name="add_new_checklist_items">Add new checklist items</string>
    <string name="checklist_is_empty">The checklist is empty</string>

    <!-- Import / Export -->
    <string name="export_all_notes">Eksportuj wszystkie notatki jako pliki</string>
    <string name="import_notes">Importuj pliki jako notatki</string>
    <string name="import_folder">Importuj folder</string>

    <!-- FAQ -->
    <string name="faq_1_title">How can I change the widgets color?</string>
    <string name="faq_1_text">In case you have only 1 active widget, you can either recreate it, or use the button in the app settings for customizing it. If you have multiple active widgets, the button in the app settings will not be available. As the app supports color customization per-widget, you will have to recreate the widget that you want to customize.</string>

    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Simple Notes Pro: To-do list organizer and planner</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Simple planner: Create notes, backup &amp; to-do lists with quick note reminder tool</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        ★ Need to take a quick note of something to buy, an address, or a startup idea? Then look no further as this is the simple organizer tool you\'ve been looking for : Simple Notes: To-do list organizer and planner! No complicated setup steps needed, just tap the screen and type in what you came for and create notes, quick lists, checklist or backup for any idea. With your simple personal notebook you can remember anything fast! Shopping for groceries, memorizing your thoughts and easier setting up reminders taking notes has never been easier ★

        Simple notes planner is quick, simple to use organizer and remarkable planner and it will serve as an invaluable tool and companion, helping you to remember necessary piece of information!

        Our reminder tool allows you to keep track of your duties,create daily checklist for items or ideas with unprecedented simplicity, notability and unrivaled time-saving value. Manage your schedule in a quick and simple manner.

        This notebook reminder tool comes with autosave so you will not discard your changes by mistake. It also supports creating multiple independent plain text notes and lists very fast.

        You can easily access the note and organize your to-do list in no time by using the customizable and resizable widget, which opens the app on tap.

        It is user friendly and contains absolutely no ads or unnecessary permissions - no strings attached. It is fully opensource, provides customizable colors which can be adjusted with quick and fast tweaking.

        <b>Simple Notes: To-do list organizer and planner</b> is the best item organizer and list planner you can use with no ads. If you need a high quality organizer for a quick and goodnotes, a reliable and user friendly reminder that is truly simple to use, download our app right now :) Have your own personal notebook in your pocket every day and have a backup planner so you will not have to worry about forgetting an important meeting or your shopping list :).

        It comes with material design and dark theme by default, provides great user experience for easy usage. The lack of internet access gives you more privacy, security and stability than other apps.

        Aplikacja nie zawiera żadnych żadnych reklam i nie potrzebuje masy uprawnień. Jest w pełni otwartoźródłowa. Posiada ciemny motyw dla osób z wrażliwymi oczami.

        <b>Check out the full suite of Simple Tools here:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Standalone website of Simple Notes Pro:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com/notes

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>

    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
